siteintelgroup.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At SITE Intelligence Group we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

SITE Intelligence Group Inc. ("SITE Intelligence Group") operates the website news.siteintelgroup.com. It is SITE Intelligence Group's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, SITE Intelligence Group collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SITE Intelligence Group's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SITE Intelligence Group's visitors use its website. From time to time, SITE Intelligence Group may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

SITE Intelligence Group also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments. SITE Intelligence Group only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to SITE Intelligence Group's websites choose to interact with SITE Intelligence Group in ways that require SITE Intelligence Group to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SITE Intelligence Group gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our newsletter at news.siteintelgroup.com to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with SITE Intelligence Group – by purchasing access to a subscription at news.siteintelgroup.com, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SITE Intelligence Group collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with SITE Intelligence Group. SITE Intelligence Group does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

SITE Intelligence Group may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. SITE Intelligence Group may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SITE Intelligence Group does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

SITE Intelligence Group discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SITE Intelligence Group's behalf or to provide services available at SITE Intelligence Group's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SITE Intelligence Group's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SITE Intelligence Group will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SITE Intelligence Group discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SITE Intelligence Group believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SITE Intelligence Group, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SITE Intelligence Group website and have supplied your email address, SITE Intelligence Group may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with SITE Intelligence Group and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SITE Intelligence Group takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SITE Intelligence Group uses cookies to help SITE Intelligence Group identify and track visitors, their usage of SITE Intelligence Group website, and their website access preferences. SITE Intelligence Group visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SITE Intelligence Group's websites, with the drawback that certain features of SITE Intelligence Group's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If SITE Intelligence Group, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that SITE Intelligence Group goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of SITE Intelligence Group may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SITE Intelligence Group and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SITE Intelligence Group may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SITE Intelligence Group's sole discretion. SITE Intelligence Group encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
